Renaissance architecture photograph collection (Holland-Yugoslavia and Latin America)
Yale University Arts Library
Renaissance architecture photograph collection (Holland-Yugoslavia and Latin America)
1900-2005
VRC 34.3
Yale University Arts Library
36.25
87 boxes (Boxes 49-136 of 136)
Collection consists of black and white and color reproductions of Renaissance architecture. Section III includes Holland-Yugoslavia and Latin America. Content varies from original photographic prints to reproductions from magazines and other published sources. Some sections have accompanying clippings folders.
Conditions Governing Access
These materials are stored offsite at the Library Shelving Facility. For access to the materials, please make a request at the Art & Architecture Library.
Arrangement
Arranged alphabetically by country. Further sub-divided by location, building type, and building name.
Scope and Contents
Collection consists of black and white and color reproductions of Renaissance architecture. Section III includes Holland-Yugoslavia and Latin America. Content varies from original photographic prints to reproductions from magazines and other published sources. Some sections have accompanying clippings folders.
Architecture, Renaissance; Photographs; Reproductions
- Architecture: Renaissance III. (Box 49)
  - Holland., 21 (Box 49)
    Scope and Contents
    Includes a folder of miscellaneous clippings.
    - General information., 1 (Box 49)
    - Miscellaneous locations., 20 (Box 49)
      - Amsterdam., 6 (Box 49)
      - Curacao (Dutch West Indies)., 1 (Box 49)
      - Dutch Cape Settlement, Africa., 2 (Box 49)
      - Haarlem., 1 (Box 49)
      - The Hague., 6 (Box 49)
      - Leiden., 3 (Box 49)
      - Maastricht., 1 (Box 49)
  - Hungary. (Box 49)
  - Italy., 3804 (Box 49)
    - General information and miscellaneous buildings., 4 (Box 49)
    - Architects., 77 (Box 49)
      - Miscellaneous architects., 24 (Box 49)
        - Unknown., 1 (Box 49)
        - Alberti, Leon, 1404-1484., 2 (Box 49)
        - Bibiena family., 3 (Box 49)
        - Borromini, Francesco, 1599-1667., 1 (Box 49)
        - Bramante, Donato, 1444-1514., 2 (Box 49)
        - Filarete (Antonio di Piero Averlino), c.1400-1469., 1 (Box 49)
        - Juvarra, Filippo, 1678-1736., 2 (Box 49)
        - Michelangelo, 1475-1564., 6 (Box 49)
        - Peruzzi, Baldassare, 1481-1536., 1 (Box 49)
        - San Gallo, Guil. da, 1445-1516., 1 (Box 49)
        - Sanmicheli, M., 1489-1554., 1 (Box 49)
        - Scamozzi, Vincenzo, 1552-1616., 1 (Box 49)
        - Serlio, Sebastiano, 1475-1554., 1 (Box 49)
        - Vignola, G. B., 1507-1572., 1 (Box 49)
      - Individual architects., 53 (Box 49)
        - Bernini, Giovanni Lorenzo, 1598-1680., 9 (Box 49)
        - Guarini, Guarino, 1624-1683., 17 (Box 49)
        - Leonardo da Vinci, 1452-1519., 14 (Box 50)
        - Palladio, Andrea, 1518-1580., 13 (Box 50)
          Includes a large folder of miscellaneous clippings.
    - Architectural ornament., 17 (Box 50)
    - Miscellaneous locations., 78 (Box 50)
      - Acqui., 1 (Box 50)
      - Ancona., 1 (Box 50)
      - Aquila., 1 (Box 50)
      - Ariccia., 2 (Box 50)
      - Asolo., 1 (Box 50)
      - Badia di Montecassino., 1 (Box 50)
      - Badoere, Treviso., 1 (Box 50)
      - Bagheria., 2 (Box 50)
      - Benevento., 1 (Box 50)
      - Bisuschio., 1 (Box 50)
      - Bolsena., 1 (Box 50)
      - Bracciano., 1 (Box 50)
      - Bramante., 1 (Box 50)
      - Brignano., 1 (Box 50)
      - Capraroloa., 1 (Box 50)
      - Carignano., 1 (Box 50)
      - Carpi., 2 (Box 50)
      - Carrara., 1 (Box 51)
      - Castiglione Fiorentino., 1 (Box 51)
      - Cercina, near Florence., 1 (Box 51)
      - Colle di Val d'Elsa., 1 (Box 51)
      - Cori., 1 (Box 51)
      - Crema., 1 (Box 51)
      - Erice, Sicily., 1 (Box 51)
      - Faenza., 3 (Box 51)
      - Fanzolo., 3 (Box 51)
      - Fermo, Marches., 1 (Box 51)
      - Foiano della Chiana., 1 (Box 51)
      - Fratta Polesine., 2 (Box 51)
      - Grado., 1 (Box 51)
      - Grottaferrata., 1 (Box 51)
      - Lonedo., 1 (Box 51)
      - Lugano., 1 (Box 51)
      - Malta., 1 (Box 51)
      - Marmirolo., 1 (Box 51)
      - Massa Marittima., 1 (Box 51)
      - Messina., 1 (Box 51)
      - Mongiovino., 1 (Box 51)
      - Montecchio Maggiore, Vincenza., 1 (Box 51)
      - Monza., 1 (Box 51)
      - Narni., 1 (Box 51)
      - Novara., 1 (Box 51)
      - Pedavena., 1 (Box 51)
      - Pescia., 1 (Box 51)
      - Poiana Maggiore., 1 (Box 51)
      - Pola., 1 (Box 51)
      - Rovigo., 1 (Box 51)
      - Sampierdarena., 1 (Box 51)
      - San Giovanni Valdarno., 1 (Box 51)
      - Sansepolcro., 2 (Box 51)
      - Santa Sophia., 1 (Box 51)
      - Sarcedo., 1 (Box 51)
      - Sarzana., 1 (Box 51)
      - Sassuolo., 1 (Box 51)
      - Savona., 1 (Box 51)
      - Sorrento., 1 (Box 51)
      - Stra., 2 (Box 51)
      - Subiaco., 1 (Box 51)
      - Syracuse., 2 (Box 51)
      - Taranto., 1 (Box 51)
      - Terni., 1 (Box 51)
      - Terracina., 1 (Box 51)
      - Trevi., 1 (Box 51)
      - Valsanzibo., 1 (Box 51)
      - Vancimulglio., 1 (Box 51)
      - Varese., 1 (Box 51)
      - Vicovaro., 1 (Box 51)
    - Individual locations., 3628 (Box 51)
      - Arezzo., 13 (Box 51)
        - Miscellaneous buildings., 10 (Box 51)
        - Santa Maria delle Grazie., 3 (Box 51)
      - Assisi., 11 (Box 51)
        - Miscellaneous buildings., 8 (Box 51)
        - Santa Maria degli Angeli., 3 (Box 52)
      - Bagnaia., 20 (Box 52)
        - Villa Lante., 20 (Box 52)
      - Bergamo., 11 (Box 52)
        - Miscellaneous buildings., 1 (Box 52)
        - Colleoni Chapel., 4 (Box 52)
        - Santa Maria Maggiore., 6 (Box 52)
      - Bologna., 87 (Box 52)
        - Miscellaneous buildings, views and details., 10 (Box 52)
        - Churches., 25 (Box 52)
          - Miscellaneous churches., 10 (Box 52)
          - Corpus Domini., 3 (Box 52)
          - San Domenico., 4 (Box 53)
          - San Martino Maggiore., 4 (Box 53)
          - San Michele in Bosco., 4 (Box 53)
        - Houses., 9 (Box 53)
          - Miscellaneous houses., 7 (Box 53)
          - Casa Caracci., 2 (Box 53)
        - Palaces., 43 (Box 53)
          - Miscellaneous palazzi., 24 (Box 53)
          - Palazzo Bevilacqua., 6 (Box 53)
          - Palazzo Bolognini., 5 (Box 53)
          - Palazzo della Divisione Militare., 3 (Box 53)
          - Palazzo Fava., 5 (Box 53)
      - Brescia., 21 (Box 53)
        - Miscellaneous buildings., 7 (Box 54)
        - Palazzo Municipale., 8 (Box 54)
        - Santa Maria dei Miracola., 6 (Box 54)
      - Bomarzo., 11 (Box 54)
      - Brindisi., 3 (Box 54)
      - Carprarola., 12 (Box 54)
        - Villa Farnese., 12 (Box 54)
      - Careggi., 4 (Box 54)
        - Villa Medici., 4 (Box 54)
      - Caserta., 30 (Box 55)
        - Palazzo Reale., 30 (Box 55)
      - Castello., 2 (Box 55)
      - Castiglione d'Olona., 2 (Box 55)
      - Citta di Castello., 7 (Box 55)
      - Collodi., 2 (Box 55)
      - Como., 25 (Box 55)
        - Miscellaneous buildings., 2 (Box 55)
        - Cathedral., 23 (Box 55)
          - Exterior., 20 (Box 55)
          - Interior., 3 (Box 55)
      - Corneto., 5 (Box 55)
      - Cortona., 8 (Box 55)
        - Miscellaneous buildings., 4 (Box 55)
        - Santa Maria Nuova., 4 (Box 55)
      - Cremona., 8 (Box 56)
      - Fano., 2 (Box 56)
      - Ferrara., 13 (Box 56)
        - Miscellaneous buildings., 7 (Box 56)
        - Palazzo dei Diamanti., 5 (Box 56)
        - Palazzo Sacrati., 1 (Box 56)
      - Fiesole., 25 (Box 56)
        - Miscellaneous buildings., 1 (Box 56)
        - Badia., 18 (Box 56)
          - Miscellaneous views and plans., 7 (Box 56)
          - Interior., 11 (Box 56)
        - Cathedral., 6 (Box 56)
      - Florence., 601 (Box 56)
        Includes two folders of miscellaneous clippings.
        - General views, plans, and architectural details., 18 (Box 57)
        - Bridges., 6 (Box 57)
        - Churches., 258 (Box 57)
          - Miscellaneous churches., 12 (Box 57)
          - Church of the Badia., 12 (Box 57)
          - Casa dell'Opera del Battistero., 2 (Box 57)
          - Cathedral., 15 (Box 57)
          - Certosa., 5 (Box 57)
          - Chiesa del Carmine., 2 (Box 57)
            - Miscellaneous views., 1 (Box 57)
            - Brancacci Chapel., 1 (Box 58)
          - Chiesa di Monte Oliveto., 1 (Box 58)
          - Church of Ognissanti., 2 (Box 58)
          - Ss. Annunziata., 10 (Box 58)
          - Santa Croce., 42 (Box 58)
            - Miscellaneous views., 15 (Box 58)
            - Pazzi Chapel., 27 (Box 58)
              - Plans and sections., 2 (Box 58)
              - Exterior and portico., 17 (Box 58)
              - Interior., 8 (Box 58)
          - San Lorenzo., 55 (Box 58)
            - Plans, sections and miscellaneous views., 26 (Box 59)
            - Old Sacristy., 7 (Box 59)
            - New Sacristy (Medici Chapel)., 8 (Box 59)
            - Laurentian Library., 14 (Box 59)
          - San Marco., 11 (Box 59)
          - Santa Maria Novella., 15 (Box 59)
          - San Pancrazio., 3 (Box 60)
          - Santo Spirito., 69 (Box 60)
            - Miscellaneous views., 27 (Box 60)
            - Architectural details., 42 (Box 60)
          - San Trinita., 2 (Box 61)
        - Clubs., 3 (Box 61)
          - Casino Mediceo., 3 (Box 61)
        - Fountains., 2 (Box 61)
        - Hospitals., 5 (Box 61)
          - Miscellaneous hospitals., 1 (Box 61)
          - Hospital of the Innocents., 4 (Box 61)
        - Loggia., 9 (Box 61)
        - Museums., 11 (Box 61)
          - Accademia., 4 (Box 61)
          - Museo Nazionale., 7 (Box 61)
        - Palaces., 270 (Box 61)
          - Miscellaneous palazzi., 21 (Box 61)
          - Palazzo Antinori., 2 (Box 61)
          - Palazzo Arcivescovile., 3 (Box 61)
          - Palazzo Bartolini., 6 (Box 62)
          - Palazzo Bartolomei., 3 (Box 62)
          - Palazzo Cavoni., 3 (Box 62)
          - Palazzo Corsi., 3 (Box 62)
          - Palazzo Corsini., 3 (Box 62)
          - Palazzo Cuccoli-Fiaschi., 2 (Box 62)
          - Palazzo Davanzati., 8 (Box 62)
          - Palazzo Fenzi., 4 (Box 62)
          - Palazzo Giugni., 3 (Box 62)
          - Palazzo Gondi., 20 (Box 62)
          - Palazzo Guadagni., 4 (Box 62)
          - Palazzo Larderell., 3 (Box 62)
          - Palazzo Mannelli., 3 (Box 63)
          - Palazzo Medici-Riccardi., 28 (Box 63)
          - Palazzo Pandolfini., 2 (Box 63)
          - Palazzo Pitti., 49 (Box 63)
            - Exterior., 27 (Box 63)
              - Miscellaneous views., 10 (Box 63)
              - Boboli Gardens., 17 (Box 63)
            - Interior., 22 (Box 64)
          - Palazzo Quaratesi., 5 (Box 64)
          - Palazzo Ramirez de'Montalvo., 5 (Box 64)
          - Palazzo Rucellai., 4 (Box 64)
          - Palazzo San Clemente., 1 (Box 64)
          - Palazzo Sertini., 2 (Box 64)
          - Palazzo Strozzi., 15 (Box 64)
          - Palazzo Torrigiani., 1 (Box 64)
          - Palazzo Uffizi., 24 (Box 64)
          - Palazzo Uguccioni., 2 (Box 65)
          - Palazzo Vecchio., 41 (Box 65)
            - Miscellaneous views., 19 (Box 65)
            - Sculptural details., 22 (Box 65)
        - Squares., 8 (Box 65)
        - Towers., 1 (Box 65)
        - Villas., 10 (Box 65)
          - Miscellaneous villas., 6 (Box 65)
          - Villa Fabricotti., 2 (Box 65)
          - Villino Favard., 1 (Box 65)
          - Villa Poggio Imperiale., 1 (Box 66)
      - Foligno., 3 (Box 66)
      - Forli., 3 (Box 66)
      - Frascati., 26 (Box 66)
        - Miscellaneous villas., 3 (Box 66)
        - Villa Aldobrandini., 10 (Box 66)
        - Villa Falconiere., 4 (Box 66)
        - Villa Mondragone., 3 (Box 66)
        - Villa Torlonia., 6 (Box 66)
      - Genoa., 68 (Box 66)
        - Miscellaneous views, buildings and plans., 6 (Box 66)
        - Porta Pila., 2 (Box 66)
        - Churches., 14 (Box 66)
          - Miscellaneous churches., 8 (Box 66)
          - San Lorenzo., 6 (Box 67)
        - Palaces., 46 (Box 67)
          - Miscellaneous palazzi., 15 (Box 67)
            - Palazzo Cambiaso., 2 (Box 67)
            - Palazzo Cataldi., 2 (Box 67)
            - Palazzo Danovaro., 1 (Box 67)
            - Palazzo Doria-Pamphili., 12 (Box 67)
            - Palazzo Imperiale., 1 (Box 67)
            - Palazzo Negrone., 3 (Box 67)
            - Palazzo Pallavicini., 1 (Box 67)
            - Palazzo Reale., 4 (Box 67)
            - Palazzo dell'Universita., 5 (Box 67)
      - Gubbio., 6 (Box 67)
      - Impruneta., 2 (Box 67)
      - Isola Bella., 4 (Box 68)
      - Lecce., 11 (Box 68)
        - Miscellaneous buildings., 4 (Box 68)
        - Santa Croce., 1 (Box 68)
        - San Nicolo e Cataldo., 2 (Box 68)
        - Palazzo della Prefettura., 2 (Box 68)
        - Palazzo del Seminario., 2 (Box 68)
      - Lodi., 3 (Box 68)
        - Palazzo Ghisalberti., 3 (Box 68)
      - Loreto., 5 (Box 68)
      - Lucca., 26 (Box 68)
        - Miscellaneous buildings., 1 (Box 68)
        - Churches., 7 (Box 68)
        - Palaces and villas., 18 (Box 68)
          - Miscellaneous palazzi and villas., 16 (Box 68)
          - Palazzo Mansi a Pellegrino., 2 (Box 68)
      - Macerata., 4 (Box 68)
      - Mantua., 107 (Box 68)
        - Miscellaneous buildings., 5 (Box 68)
        - San Andrea., 17 (Box 69)
        - San Sebastiano., 5 (Box 69)
        - Ducal Palace., 45 (Box 69)
          - Exterior., 3 (Box 69)
          - Interior., 42 (Box 69)
            - Miscellaneous views., 17 (Box 70)
            - Ceiling details., 25 (Box 70)
        - Palazzo del Te., 35 (Box 70)
          - Exterior., 12 (Box 70)
          - Interior., 23 (Box 70)
            - Miscellaneous views., 10 (Box 70)
            - Sala di Cesare., 3 (Box 70)
            - Sala di Fetonte., 5 (Box 70)
            - Loggia., 5 (Box 70)
      - Maser., 11 (Box 70)
      - Milan., 70 (Box 70)
        - Miscellaneous buildings., 25 (Box 70)
        - Castle Sforza., 6 (Box 70)
        - Santa Maria delle Grazie., 11 (Box 71)
        - San Satiro., 15 (Box 71)
        - Ospedale Maggiore., 8 (Box 71)
        - Palazzo del Scuola Palatina., 1 (Box 71)
        - Palazzo Marino., 4 (Box 71)
      - Mira., 11 (Box 71)
      - Modena., 5 (Box 71)
      - Montecassino., 7 (Box 71)
        - Miscellaneous buildings., 1 (Box 71)
        - Badia., 6 (Box 71)
      - Montepulciano., 23 (Box 71)
        - Miscellaneous buildings., 12 (Box 71)
        - San Biagio., 11 (Box 72)
      - Monte San Savino., 4 (Box 72)
      - Naples., 95 (Box 72)
        - Miscellaneous buildings and views., 9 (Box 72)
        - Churches., 53 (Box 72)
          - Miscellaneous churches., 15 (Box 72)
          - Cathedral., 11 (Box 72)
          - Certosa of San Martino., 11 (Box 72)
          - Chiesa di San Chiara., 16 (Box 73)
        - Columns., 3 (Box 73)
        - Fountains., 3 (Box 73)
        - Museums., 5 (Box 73)
          - Miscellaneous museums., 1 (Box 73)
          - National Museum., 4 (Box 73)
        - Palaces., 22 (Box 73)
          - Miscellaneous palazzi., 5 (Box 73)
          - Palazzo di Capodimonte., 6 (Box 73)
          - Palazzo Reale., 11 (Box 73)
      - Orvieto., 1 (Box 73)
      - Padua., 16 (Box 73)
      - Palermo., 11 (Box 73)
        - Miscellaneous buildings and views., 8 (Box 73)
        - Palazzo Reale., 3 (Box 73)
      - Parma., 14 (Box 74)
      - Pavia., 53 (Box 74)
        - Miscellaneous buildings., 1 (Box 74)
        - Certosa., 50 (Box 74)
          - Exterior., 20 (Box 74)
          - Interior., 18 (Box 74)
          - Cloister., 12 (Box 74)
        - San Lanfranco., 2 (Box 74)
      - Perugia., 35 (Box 74)
        - Miscellaneous buildings and views., 6 (Box 74)
        - Church of Madonaa della Luce., 2 (Box 75)
        - Collegio del Cambio., 7 (Box 75)
        - Ss. Andrea e Bernardino., 5 (Box 75)
        - San Pietro., 15 (Box 75)
      - Pesaro., 3 (Box 75)
      - Piacenza., 3 (Box 75)
      - Pienza., 18 (Box 75)
        - Miscellaneous buildings, plans and views., 6 (Box 75)
        - Palazzo Picolomini., 12 (Box 75)
      - Pisa., 16 (Box 75)
        - Miscellaneous buildings and views., 12 (Box 75)
        - Cathedral., 4 (Box 76)
      - Pistoia., 22 (Box 76)
        - Miscellaneous buildings., 7 (Box 76)
        - Ospedale del Ceppo., 8 (Box 76)
        - Palazzo del Comune., 7 (Box 76)
      - Poggia a Caiano., 16 (Box 76)
        - Villa Medici., 16 (Box 76)
      - Prato., 11 (Box 76)
        - Cathedral., 5 (Box 76)
        - Santa Maria delle Carcere., 6 (Box 76)
      - Ravenna., 2 (Box 76)
      - Rimini., 16 (Box 76)
        - Miscellaneous views., 1 (Box 76)
        - San Francesco (Tempio Malatestiano)., 15 (Box 77)
      - Rome., 1076 (Box 77)
        - Miscellaneous buildings, views and maps., 27 (Box 77)
        - Castel Sant'Angelo., 16 (Box 77)
        - Churches., 397 (Box 77)
          - Miscellaneous churches., 26 (Box 78)
          - Collegio di Propaganda Fide., 3 (Box 78)
          - Il Gesu., 15 (Box 78)
          - Santa Agnese., 7 (Box 78)
          - San Agostino., 2 (Box 78)
          - San Alessio., 1 (Box 78)
          - San Andrea., 1 (Box 78)
          - San Andrea al Quirinale., 7 (Box 78)
          - San Andrea della Valle., 5 (Box 78)
          - San Andrea delle Fratte., 2 (Box 78)
          - San Apostoli., 6 (Box 78)
          - San Carlo a Catinari., 1 (Box 78)
          - San Carlo al Corso., 1 (Box 78)
          - San Carlo alle Quattro Fontane., 6 (Box 78)
          - Santa Caterina de'Funari., 1 (Box 78)
          - Santa Cecilia., 6 (Box 79)
          - San Damaso., 1 (Box 79)
          - Ss. Domenico e Sisto., 3 (Box 79)
          - San Francesca Romana., 1 (Box 79)
          - San Giacomo degli Spagnoli., 4 (Box 79)
          - San Giovanni Crisogono., 1 (Box 79)
          - San Giovanni in Laterano., 15 (Box 79)
          - San Giovanni in Olio., 2 (Box 79)
          - San Girolamo della Carita., 2 (Box 79)
          - San Ignazio., 8 (Box 79)
          - Sant'Ivo della Sapienza., 8 (Box 79)
          - San Marco., 3 (Box 79)
          - Santa Maria degli Angeli., 4 (Box 79)
          - Santa Maria dell'Anima.., 1 (Box 79)
          - Santa Maria in Aracoeli., 7 (Box 80)
          - Santa Maria della Consolazione., 3 (Box 80)
          - Santa Maria di Loreto., 8 (Box 80)
          - Santa Maria Maggiore., 14 (Box 80)
          - Santa Maria di Monserrato., 6 (Box 80)
          - Santa Maria dei Miracoli and Santa Maria di Monte Santo., 4 (Box 80)
          - Santa Maria della Pace., 17 (Box 80)
          - Santa Maria del Popolo., 15 (Box 81)
          - Santa Maria del Priorato., 7 (Box 81)
          - Santa Maria Sopra Minerva., 7 (Box 81)
          - Santa Maria in Trastevere., 3 (Box 81)
          - Santa Maria in Via Lata., 2 (Box 81)
          - Santa Maria della Vittoria., 6 (Box 81)
          - Saint Peter's., 129 (Box 81)
            - Miscellaneous views., 3 (Box 81)
            - Plans and models., 48 (Box 82)
            - Exterior., 43 (Box 82)
              - Miscellaneous views., 35 (Box 82)
              - Piazza., 8 (Box 82)
            - Interior., 35 (Box 83)
          - San Pietro in Montorio., 12 (Box 83)
          - San Pietro in Vincoli., 5 (Box 83)
          - San Salvatore alla Scala Santa., 1 (Box 83)
          - Santa Susanna., 4 (Box 83)
          - La Trinita dei Monti., 3 (Box 83)
          - San Vincenzo e Anastasio., 1 (Box 83)
        - Clubs., 4 (Box 83)
          - Miscellaneous clubs., 3 (Box 83)
          - Casino Spillman., 1 (Box 83)
        - Fountains., 41 (Box 83)
          - Miscellaneous fountains., 27 (Box 83)
          - Fountain of Trevi., 11 (Box 83)
          - Fontana Paola., 3 (Box 84)
        - Gates., 4 (Box 84)
        - Hospitals., 1 (Box 84)
          - Hospital of Santo Spirito in Sassia., 1 (Box 84)
        - Houses., 7 (Box 84)
          - Miscellaneous houses., 5 (Box 84)
          - Cassa Crivelli., 2 (Box 84)
        - Museums., 4 (Box 84)
          - Miscellaneous museums., 2 (Box 84)
          - Terme Museum., 2 (Box 84)
        - Palaces., 271 (Box 84)
          - Miscellaneous palazzi., 20 (Box 84)
          - Palazzo Altemps., 2 (Box 84)
          - Palazzo Barberini., 8 (Box 84)
          - Palazzo Berardi., 1 (Box 84)
          - Palazzo Borghese., 12 (Box 84)
          - Palazzo Braschi., 6 (Box 85)
          - Palazzo Caetani., 2 (Box 85)
          - Palazzo Cancelleria., 33 (Box 85)
            - Plans and sections., 1 (Box 85)
            - Exterior., 12 (Box 85)
            - Interior., 20 (Box 85)
          - Palazzo Capodiferro., 1 (Box 85)
          - Palazzo Capranica., 2 (Box 85)
          - Palazzo Cenci., 2 (Box 85)
          - Palazzo Colonna., 9 (Box 85)
          - Palazzo dei Convertendi., 1 (Box 85)
          - Palazzo della Consulta., 4 (Box 85)
          - Palazzo Doria-Pamphili., 5 (Box 86)
          - Palazzo Farnese., 42 (Box 86)
            - Plans and elevations., 2 (Box 86)
            - Exterior., 10 (Box 86)
            - Interior., 30 (Box 86)
              - Miscellaneous views., 8 (Box 86)
              - Ceilings., 10 (Box 86)
              - Courtyard., 12 (Box 86)
          - Palazzo Farri., 1 (Box 86)
          - Palazzo Giraud (now Torlonia)., 4 (Box 86)
          - Palazzo Governo Vecchio., 1 (Box 86)
          - Palazzo Lancellotti., 1 (Box 86)
          - Palazzo Laterano., 9 (Box 86)
          - Palazzo Linotta., 3 (Box 87)
          - Palazzo Maccarani., 2 (Box 87)
          - Palazzo Margherita., 1 (Box 87)
          - Palazzo Massimi., 15 (Box 87)
          - Palazzo Mattei., 18 (Box 87)
          - Palazzo Odescalchi., 2 (Box 87)
          - Palazzo Ossoli., 1 (Box 87)
          - Palazzo Poli., 1 (Box 87)
          - Palazzo dell Prefettura., 1 (Box 87)
          - Palazzo Quirinale., 10 (Box 87)
          - Palazzo Rospigliosi-Pallavicini., 6 (Box 87)
          - Palazzo di San Paolo in Trastevere., 1 (Box 87)
          - Palazzo di Papa Giulio., 1 (Box 87)
          - Palazzo Sacchetti., 4 (Box 87)
          - Palazzo Sciarra., 3 (Box 87)
          - Palazzo Spada., 15 (Box 88)
          - Palazzetto Turci., 2 (Box 88)
          - Palazzo di Venezia., 12 (Box 88)
          - Palazzo Vidoni-Caffarelli., 5 (Box 88)
          - Palazzo Zuccari., 2 (Box 88)
        - Squares., 55 (Box 88)
          - Miscellaneous squares., 3 (Box 88)
          - Piazza Campidoglio., 29 (Box 89)
          - Piazza di Monte Cavallo (Piazza Quirinale)., 2 (Box 89)
          - Piazza Navona., 4 (Box 89)
          - Piazza del Popolo., 10 (Box 89)
          - Piazza di Spagna., 7 (Box 89)
        - Vatican., 133 (Box 89)
          - Plans and maps., 5 (Box 89)
          - Exterior., 3 (Box 89)
          - Interior., 11 (Box 89)
          - Belvedere., 12 (Box 89)
          - Casino of Pius IV., 14 (Box 89)
          - Consistory., 2 (Box 90)
          - Gardens., 4 (Box 90)
          - Library., 8 (Box 90)
          - Loggia of Gergory XIII., 4 (Box 90)
          - Loggia di Raphael, 9 (Box 90)
          - Museum., 18 (Box 90)
          - Pope's Apartments., 3 (Box 90)
          - Borgia Apartments., 13 (Box 90)
          - Sala Regia., 6 (Box 91)
          - Sistine Chapel., 21 (Box 91)
        - Villas., 116 (Box 91)
          - Miscellaneous villas., 4 (Box 91)
          - Villa Albani (now Torlonia)., 20 (Box 91)
          - Villa Aurelia., 1 (Box 91)
          - Villa Borghese., 22 (Box 92)
          - Villa Farnesina., 7 (Box 92)
          - Villa Giulia., 20 (Box 92)
          - Villa Madama., 27 (Box 92)
          - Villa Medici., 11 (Box 92)
          - Villa Pamphili., 4 (Box 93)
      - Salerno. (Box 93)
      - San Remo., 4 (Box 93)
        - Miscellaneous buildings and streets., 3 (Box 93)
        - Via Umberto., 1 (Box 93)
      - Santa Catarina del Sasso., 1 (Box 93)
      - San Gimignano., 1 (Box 93)
      - Sassovivo., 1 (Box 93)
      - Settignano., 4 (Box 93)
        - Villa di Gamberaia., 4 (Box 93)